Harvard University. Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008: an inventory
Official register of Harvard University, 1900-2008
- Volume XXVIII, issued 1931
  - 7. Rules relating to College studies, 1931, March 4, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 8. General examinations and tutors in Harvard College, March 11, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 9. Information in regard to freshman halls, March 16, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 10. Division of Sociology, 1931-1932, March 25, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 11. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1931-1932, first edition, March 26, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 12. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1931-1932, March 30, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 13. Announcement of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1931, March 31, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 14. The Law School, 1931-1932, April 17, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 15. Division of Mathematics, 1931-1932, April 23, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 16. The Theological School, 1931-1932,April 24, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 17. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1931-1932, April 25, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 18. Description of opportunities for voluntary work offered at the Harvard Medical School, 1931-1932, April 27, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 19. Division of Anthropology, 1931-1932, April 28, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 21. Graduate School of Education, 1931-1932, April 30, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 22. School of Landscape Architecture, 1931-1932, May 21, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 23. Division of the Fine Arts, 1931-1932, May 22, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 24. School of City Planning, 1931-1932, May 23, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 25. Division of History, Government, and Economics, 1931-1932, May 25, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 26. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, 1931-1932, May 26, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 27. The Harvard School of Public Health, 1931-1932, May 27, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 28. Faculty of Architecture, School of Architecture, 1931-1932, May 28, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 29. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1931, May 29, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 30. The Institute of Criminal Law of the Law School, 1931-1932, June 18, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 31. Announcement of courses in the Harvard Engineering School, 1931-1932, June 22, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 32. Division of Chemistry, 1931-1932, June 23, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 33. Division of Music, 1931-1932, June 24, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 34. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, 1931-1932, June 25, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 35. Concentration field of biochemical sciences, 1931-1932, June 26, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 36. Department of English, 1931-1932, June 27, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 37. Announcement of the courses offered by the Department of Military Science and Tactics of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1931-1932, June 29, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 38. Harvard College rank list for 1930-1931, July 29, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 39. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1931-1932, July 30, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 40. Graduate School of Business Administration, rank list for 1930-1931, July 31, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 41. Division of Physical Sciences, Department of Physics, Department of Astronomy and Department of Engineering Sciences, 1931-1932, August 20, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 42. Department of Naval Science and Tactics, 1931-1932, August 25, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 43. Division of Geology, Departments of Geology and Geography, and Mineralogy and Petrography, 1931-1932, August 28, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 43, Supplement. Division of Geology, August 28, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 44. Division of Sociology, 1931-1932, September 16, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 45. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1931-1932, second edition, September 24, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 48. The Medical School, 1931-1932, with an announcement for 1932-1933, November 30, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 49. Admission to Harvard College and the Harvard Engineering School, December 12, 1931 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
- Volume XXIX, issued 1932
  - 1. The Dental School, 1931-1932, January 11, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 2. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1930-1931, January 29, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 51)
  - 3. Provisional announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1932-1933, February 26, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 4. Rules relating to College studies, 1932, February 27, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 5. The houses, general information for the Class of 1935, February 29, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 5. Information in regard to the freshman halls with floor plans and prices, February 29, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 6. Department of Engineering Sciences, 1932-1933, March 21, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 7. Announcement of the Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1932, March 24, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 8. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1932-1933, first edition, March 26, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 9. General examinations and tutors in Harvard College, March 28, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 10. The Theological School, 1932-1933, March 29, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 11. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College and other departments of the University, 1932, March 30, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 12. City planning as a professional career, by Henry V. Hubbard and Howard K. Menhinick, April 22, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 13. Division of Anthropology, 1932-1933,April 23, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 14. The Law School, 1932-1933, April 25, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 15. Faculty of Architecture, School of Architecture, 1932-1933, April 26, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 16. Division of Sociology, 1932-1933, April 27, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 17. Institute of Criminal Law of the Law School, 1932-1933, April 28, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 18. Undergraduate School of Engineering, April 29, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 19. Division of Mathematics, 1932-1933, April 30, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 20. School of City Planning, 1932-1933, May 21, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 21. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Engineering, 1932-1933, May 23, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 22. School of Landscape Architecture, 1932-1933, May 24, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 23. Graduate School of Engineering, 1932-1933, May 25, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 24. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Department of Military Science and Tactics of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1932-1933, May 25, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 25. Division of Music, 1932-1933, May 27, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 26. Division of the Fine Arts, 1932-1933, May 28, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 27. The Harvard School of Public Health, 1932-1933, May 31, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 28. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1932, June 22, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 29. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1932-1933, June 23, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 30. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1932-1933, June 24, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 31. Graduate School of Education, 1932-1933, June 25, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 32. Division of History, Government, and Economics, 1932-1933, June 27, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 33. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, 1932-1933, June 28, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 34. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, 1932-1933, June 29, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 35. Department of English, 1932-1933, June 30, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 36. Harvard College rank list for 1931-1932, July 5, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 37. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1932-1933, July 28, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 38. Division of Physical Sciences, Department of Physics and Department of Astronomy, 1932-1933, July 30, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 39. Department of Naval Science and Tactics, 1932-1933, August 13, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 40. Division of Chemistry, 1932-1933, August 31, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 41. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1932-1933, second edition, September 19, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 42. The Harvard Medical School, 1932-1933, October 17, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 44. Harvard College in Harvard University, general information, 1932, November 30, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 45. Admission to Harvard College and the Harvard Engineering School, 1933, December 3, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
  - 47. Division of Medical Sciences, 1932-1933,December 14, 1932 (HU 75.25 Box 53)
- Volume XXX, issued 1933
  - 1. Report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments, 1931-1932, January 31, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 52)
  - 2. The houses, general information for the Class of 1936, February 8, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 3. Information in regard to the freshman halls, with floor plans and prices, 1933, February 11, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 4. Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1933, February 28, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 5. Rules relating to College studies, 1933, March 8, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 6. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1933-1934, first edition, March 15, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 7. Division of Anthropology, 1933-1934, March 22, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 8. The Dental School, 1932-1933, March 27, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 9. Division of Sociology, 1933-1934, March 28, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 10. Announcement of courses offered by the Faculty of Engineering, 1933-1934, March 29, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 11. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College and other departments of the University, 1933, March 30, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 12. Graduate School of Engineering, 1933-1934, March 31, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 13. The Law School, 1933-1934, April 21, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 14. Undergraduate School of Engineering, 1933-1934, April 22, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 15. School of City Planning, 1933-1934, April 24, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 16. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, 1933-1934, April 25, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 17. Department of Engineering Sciences, 1933-1934, April 26, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 18. Division of Music, 1933-1934, April 27, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 19. School of Landscape Architecture, 1933-1934, April 28, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 20. Faculty of Architecture, School of Architecture, 1933-1934, April 29, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 21. Department of Military Science, 1933-1934, May 15, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 22. Division of Philosophy, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, 1933-1934,May 22, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 23. The Harvard School of Public Health, 1933-1934, May 23, 1922 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 24. Division of Geological Sciences, Department of Geology and Geography, Mineralogy and Petrography, 1933-1934, May 24, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 25. Division of Mathematics, 1933-1934, May 25, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 26. The Divinity School, 1933-1934, May 26, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 27. The Graduate School of Business Administration, 1933, May 29, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 28. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, 1933-1934, May 31, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 29. Division of Biology, Departments of Botany, Zoology, Physiology and related institutions, 1933-1934, June 21, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 30. Graduate School of Education, 1933, June 22, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 31. Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1933-1934, June 24, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 32. Department of English, 1933-1934, June 26, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 33. Division of History, Government, and Economics, 1933-1934, June 27, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 34. Division of Chemistry, 1933-1934, June 28, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 35. Department of Astronomy, 1933-1934, June 29, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 36. Department of Physics, 1933-1934, June 30, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 37. Harvard College rank list for 1932-1933, July 27, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 38. Department of Naval Science and Tactics, 1933-1934, July 28, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 39. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1933-1934, second edition, September 20, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 40. The Harvard Medical School, 1933-1934, with an announcement for 1934-1935, October 14, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 43. Harvard College in Harvard University, general information, 1933, December 23, 1933 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
- Volume XXXI, issued 1934
  No 47 was never printed.
  Beginning with Volume XXXI, the rank list excludes the three upper classes, listing freshmen only.
  - 1. The Dental School, 1933-1934, January 17, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 2. Admission to Harvard College and the Harvard Engineering School, 1934, January 20, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 4. Information in regard to freshman halls, with floor plans and prices, 1934, February 9, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 5. The houses, general information for the Class of 1937, March 1, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 6. Rules relating to College studies, 1934, March 2, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 7. The Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1934, March 3, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 8. Department of Engineering Sciences, 1934-1935, March 10, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 9. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1934-1935, first edition, March 15, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 10. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College and other departments of the University, March 16, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 11. Undergraduate School of Engineering, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, March 20, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 12. Division of Anthropology, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, March 30, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 13. General examinations and tutors in Harvard College, April 20, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 14. Graduate School of Engineering, including announcement of courses under the Faculty of Engineering, 1934-1935, April 23, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 15. School of City Planning including courses of instruction for 1934-1935, April 24, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 16. Department of Physics, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, April 25, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 17. Division of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Philosophy and Psychology, 1934-1935, April 26, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 18. Division of Music, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, April 27, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 19. School of Architecture with courses of instruction for 1934-1935, April 28, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 20. The Law School, including courses of instruction for 1934-1935, April 30, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 21. School of Landscape Architecture with courses of instruction for 1934-1935, May 18, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 22. Division of Mathematics containing an announcement for 1934-1935, May 21, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 23. The School of Public Health including courses of instruction for 1934-1935, May 24, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 24. Division of the Fine Arts containing an announcement for 1934-1935, May 25, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 25. Department of Military Sciences containing an announcement for 1934-1935, May 26, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 26. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1934-1935, May 28, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 27. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, May 29, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 28. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, May 31, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 29. Divinity School, including courses of instruction for 1934-1935, June 22, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 30. Division of Chemistry, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, June 23, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 31. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, June 25, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 32. Department of English, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, June 26, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 33. Division of History, Government, and Economics, containing an announcement for 1934-1935,June 27, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 34. Department of Naval Science and Tactics, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, June 28, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 35. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, June 29, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 36. Harvard College rank list for freshman class (Class of 1937), June 30, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 37. Division of Sociology, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, July 30, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 38. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1934-1935, second edition, September 20, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 39. The Harvard Medical School, with an announcement for 1935-1936, September 21, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 40. Department of Astronomy, containing an announcement for 1934-1935, November 1, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 41. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College and other departments of the University, November 2, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 43. Engineering undergraduate preparation, December 1, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 44. Statement of the Treasurer of Harvard College for the fiscal year, 1933-1934, October 30, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 45. Admission to Harvard College, containing requirements for the academic year 1935-1936, December 12, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 46. General examinations and tutors in Harvard College, 1934, October 31, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 48. Harvard College in Harvard University, general information, August 31, 1934 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
- Volume XXXII, issued 1935
  - 1. The Dental School, January 17, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 2. Information in regard to the freshman halls, with floor plans and prices, 1935, January 15, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 3. Issue containing the report of the President of Harvard College and reports of departments for 1933-1934, February 18, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 54)
  - 4. The houses, general information for the Class of 1938, February 19, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 5. Rules relating to College studies, 1935, March 1, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 6. Graduate School of Business Administration, 1935, March 2, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 7. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1935-1936, first edition, March 4, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 8. Division of Engineering Sciences, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, March 5, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 9. Division of Geological Sciences, Departments of Geology and Geography and Mineralogy and Petrography, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, March 11, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 10. Summer School of Arts and Sciences and of Education, 1935, March 14, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 12. Department of Physics, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, March 30, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 13. Division of Music, April 22, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 14. The Law School, including courses of instruction for 1935-1936,April 23, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 15. Division of Anthropology, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, April 24, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 16. Expenses and financial aids in Harvard College and other departments of the University, April 25, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 17. Graduate School of Landscape Architecture, with courses of instruction for 1935-1936, April 26, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 18. Division of Philosophy and Psychology, Department of Philosophy, Department of Psychology, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, April 27, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 19. Division of Mathematics, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, April 28, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 20. Division of the Fine Arts, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, April 30, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 20. Graduate School of Architecture, with courses of instruction for 1935-1936, April 14, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 21. Graduate School of City Planning, including courses of instruction for 1935-1936, May 22, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 22. Division of Ancient Languages, Department of the Classics and Department of Indic Philology, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, May 23, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 23. University training for government service, May 24, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 24. The Divinity School, including courses of instruction for 1935-1936, May 25, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 25. Graduate School of Engineering, including announcement of courses under the Faculty of Engineering, 1935-1936, May 27, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 26. Graduate School of Education, including courses of instruction for 1935-1936, May 28, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 27. The Harvard School of Public Health, including courses of instruction for 1935-1936, May 29, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 28. Division of Biology and related institutions, including courses of instruction for 1935-1936, May 31, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 29. Department of Military Science, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, June 21, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 30. Regulations for the degree of Ph.D. in the history of science and learning, June 22, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 31. Division of Sociology, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, June 24, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 32. Graduate School of Architecture, with courses of instruction for 1935-1936, June 25, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 33. Studies in the freshman year in Harvard College, June 26, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 34. Department of Romance Languages and Literatures, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, June 27, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 35. Division of Chemistry, containing an announcement for 1935-1936,June 28, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 36. Harvard College rank list for freshman class (Class of 1938), June 29, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 37. Division of History, Government and Economics, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, July 30, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 38. Department of Naval Science and Tactics, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, July 31, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 39. Department of English, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, August 14, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 40. The Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, August 15, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 41. Department of Germanic Languages and Literatures, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, September 14, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 42. Announcement of the courses of instruction offered by the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1935-1936, second edition, September 18, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 43. Department of Astronomy, containing an announcement for 1935-1936, October 1, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 44. Directory of officers and students, October 18, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 45. The Harvard Medical School, with an announcement for 1936-1937, November 1, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
  - 47. Statement of the Treasurer of Harvard College for the fiscal year 1934-1935, December 14, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 55)
  - 48. The Dental School, December 31, 1935 (HU 75.25 Box 56)
- Volume XXXIII, issued 1936
  - 1. Admission to Harvard College, containing requirements for the academic year 1936-1937, January 10, 1936 (HU 75.25 Box 58)
  - 2. Information in regard to the freshman halls with floor plans and prices, January 23, 1936 (HU 75.25 Box 58)